(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-25T10:38:08.238785",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": false,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": false
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
輪堂千速生誕祭2026 FlatOut Summeres
Chihaya Rindou Birthday Festival 2026 FlatOut Summeres
リミット外せ！
Remove the limits!
生誕2026を祝ってくれてありがとう！
Thank you for celebrating my 2026 birthday!
盛り上がる準備できてんのか！？
Are you ready to get hyped!?
ブチ上げていくぞ！
Let's turn it up!
でも、ちょっと今から1人でライブ会場にみんなを連れて行かなきゃなんないから、一緒にいってくれるか？行くぞ！
Wait, since I gotta take everyone to the live venue by myself now, will you come with me? Let's go!
熱くなった銀のメタリックハート
My silver, metallic heart heated up
導火線に火をつけてあげる
I'll light the fuse
不思議なほどハイな気分さ
I feel so high it's strange
砂埃を巻き上げて行こう
Let's kick up dust and go
悲鳴をまじえ暴走する鼓動
My recklessly beating pulse blends with screams
目の前にはミサイルの雨
A rain of missiles right before my eyes
アドレナリンずっと流して
With adrenaline constantly flowing
僕の方がオーバーヒートしそう
It feels like I'm the one about to overheat
爆発して灰になっても
Even if I explode and turn to ashes
このままだと笑ってるね きっと
I'm sure I'll still be laughing just like this
街を追い越して この世の果てまで
Passing by the city, to the end of the world
ぶっ飛ばして心中しよう さぁ手を伸ばして！
Let's blast off and die together, come on, reach out your hand!
地平線に届くように 限界まで振り切ってくれ
Pushing it to the limit so we can reach the horizon
Woh! Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
最高のフィナーレを！Yeah！
Towards the best finale! Yeah!
もう数えるくらいで僕らは消え失せて真暗な朝が来るね
Soon enough we'll disappear, and a pitch-black morning will come
お気に入りの服に さぁ着かえたなら駆け出して！
Once you've changed into your favorite clothes, let's run off!
あきれるほど声を上げて大気圏を突破しようぜ
Raise your voice absurdly and break through the atmosphere!
Woh! Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
鋼の翼で
With steel wings
駆け抜けろ時間切れまで
Keep racing through until time runs out
生まれつきのスピード狂なのさ
Because we're natural-born speed demons
Woh! Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
来世でまた会おう Yeah！
See you again in the next life, Yeah!
広い宇宙の 数ある一つ
One of the many in the vast universe,
青い地球の 広い世界で
in the vast world of the blue earth,
小さな恋の 想いは届く
a small love song reaches out,
小さな島の あなたのもとへ
to you on a small island.
あなたと出会い 時は流れる
Since I met you, time flows by,
思いを込めた 手紙もふえる
and handwritten letters increase.
いつしか二人 互いに響く
Before we knew it, our hearts resonate,
時に激しく 時に切なく
sometimes intense, sometimes poignant.
響くは遠く 遥か彼方へ
Resonating far into the distant horizon,
やさしい歌は 世界を変える
a gentle song changes the world.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
See, the ones most precious to you are always right by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい 響け 恋の歌
I just want this to reach you and you alone—let the song of love ring out.
ほら…
See...
響け 恋の歌
Let the song of love ring out.
あなたは気づく 二人は歩く 暗い道でも 日々照らす月
You realize, as we walk on even through dark roads, illuminated by the moon day by day.
握りしめた手 離すことなく
Holding hands tightly without ever letting go,
思いは強く 永遠誓う
our feelings are strong, swearing an eternal vow.
永遠の淵 きっと僕は言う 思い変わらず 同じ言葉を
At the edge of eternity, I'll surely say the same words, unchanging in my feelings.
それでも足りず 涙にかわり 喜びになり
Still, it's not enough, turning into tears, turning into joy.
言葉にできず ただ抱きしめる
Unable to put it into words, I just hold you close.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
See, the ones most precious to you are right by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい 響け 恋の歌
I just want this to reach you—let the song of love ring out.
ほら…
See...
響け 恋の歌
Let the song of love ring out.
夢ならば 覚めないで
If this is a dream, please don't wake me up.
あなたと過ごした時 永遠の星となる
The time I spent with you becomes an eternal star.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
See, the ones most precious to you are right by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい 響け 恋の歌
I just want this to reach you—let the song of love ring out.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
See, the ones most precious to you are right by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ 届いて欲しい 響け 恋の歌
I just want this to reach you—let the song of love ring out.
響け 恋の歌
Let the song of love ring out.
はい！どうもありがとうございました！みなさん、輪堂千速生誕祭に お越しくださり、ありがとうございます！
Hai! Thank you so much, everyone, for coming to Rindou Chihaya's Birthday Festival!
聞こえていますでしょうかー？挨拶します！
Can you hear me? Let's say hello!
えっでか！れっつごー！
Etteka, let's go!
やばい、めちゃめちゃ緊張した！んと、輪堂千速です！こんちわー！
Yabai, I was so nervous! This is Rindou Chihaya's... Kohanchi!
ということで、始まりました！はじめての3D生誕ライブー！
So, it has begun! The very first 3D Chihaya Live!
いっぱい盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's make it super exciting!
配信のハッシュタグは、右上……あ、これ、かぎ上のこちらになります！
The stream hashtag is in the top right—no, top left? Wait, top right here!
ハッシュタグ 輪堂千速生誕祭2026 になるので、たくさんポストしていただけるととてもうれしいです！
#RindouChihayaBirthdayFes2026, so please post lots!
ちゃんと見ますからね！
I'll definitely read them!
させてもらえると、嬉しいです。
If you'll let me do this, I'm so happy.
わ、こんちはいぱいありがとうございます！
Wa, Konchi High-Five, thank you so much!
ということでね、いったんちょっと2曲歌わせていただいたので
So, we've sung two songs so far,
振り返って行こうかなと思うんですが、
and I thought we could look back at them.
まずは1曲目、ドライバーズハイをフグタローでドライブしながら
First, for the first song, Driver's High, while driving with Fugutaro,
歌わせていただきました。どうでしたでしょうか？
I sang it. How was it?
デビュ—のね、一番最初にLarcさんの曲を歌ってて
Right at my debut, I sang Larc's song first,
で、このドライバーズハイをいつか歌ってほしいってすごいいっぱい言われていたので、絶対生誕で歌おうと思って1曲目に選びました。
and since so many people asked me to sing Driver's High someday, I decided to sing it for my birthday and chose it as the first song.
いや、あの、まああのあそこカバーの自由度なので、色々もろもろひっくるめてOKです。大丈夫。きっと大丈夫。
Well, you know, since it's a cover's degree of freedom, everything included is totally fine. It's fine, surely fine.
そして2曲目は、小さな恋のうたでした。どうでしたか？
And the second song was Chiisana Koi no Uta. How was it?
そう、これ！
That's right, this!
千隼が引いてましたよ！
Chihaya played it!
いや、あの、ご存知の方も多いかなと思うんですがね、エレキを購入しまして練習していたんですが、あの、惹かせていただきました！
Well, I think many of you know, I bought an electric guitar and was practicing, and um, I played it!
やっぱり、なんかエレキで初めて挑戦するのって、なんか小さな恋の歌の歌だなあってイメージがあってこの曲を選んだんですけど、
As for the first challenge with an electric guitar, I had the image of Chiisana Koi no Uta, so I chose this song, but
すっごく難しい！すっごく難しかったんですけど、
it's so hard! It was so hard, but
でもね生誕ライブでかっこいいところ見せたかったので、いっぱい、いっぱい練習して、弾けてたよね？なんとか弾けてたと思います！
since I wanted to show a cool side of me at the birthday live, I practiced lots and lots, and I played it right? I think I managed to play it!
なのでね、いっぱいあの後アーカイブとかも見直して、聞いてくれると嬉しいです。
So I'd be happy if you rewatch the archive afterwards and listen to it.
ということで、そしてねお気づきの方もいいますが、小さな恋の歌最初体育館だったんですけど、サターンに出てきましたよ！
And as some of you noticed, Chiisana Koi no Uta started in a gymnasium, but it came out to Saturn!
やっぱ夏といえば、外、海、山、自然！そして音楽、夏の音楽といえばフェス！
Speaking of summer, outside, sea, mountains, nature! And music, summer music means festivals!
をイメージして夏フェス会場になっております！
Imagining that, it's a summer festival venue!
後ろにはね海もあって、最高のロケーションで今日はフェスを開催していければなと思っております。
Behind us, there's the ocean too, and I hope we can hold the festival today in the best location.
こんなにね広いので、あっちに行ったり、両手にない動きをしてすみません本当に。あっちに行ったりしていこうと思っています。
It's so wide, sorry for moving around to the sides, really. I plan to move around over there.
では、まちょっとあんまり喋るとあれなので、次の曲行こうと思うので、ちょっと準備するのでギターとマイク置いてきます。ちょっと待っててね、行ってきまーす。
Well, talking too much is no good, so I'm going to the next song, getting ready, so I'll leave the guitar and mic. Wait a second, I'll be right back.
はい、ということで、はい、来ました来ました。
Yes, so, yes, I'm back.
ということでここからはですねゲストブロックになりますので、この後もいっぱい楽しんでいってください。
So from here on is the guest block, so please enjoy the rest as well.
盛り上がって行くぞー！バイバーイ！
Let's get hyped! Bye-bye!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are fighting dreamers, aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting dreamers, don't care what people think
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting dreamers, follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here Right now
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna get the fire!
Right here Right now
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna get the fire!
険しい修羅の道のなか 他人の地図を広げて何処へ行く?
Down a difficult road filled with endless struggles, where are you going following someone else's map?
極彩色のからすがそれを奪い取って破り捨てた
A wise crow comes along to tear up the map
さあ心の目 見開いて しかと今を見極めろ!
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth!
失うモノなんてないさ いざ参らん!
There's nothing to lose, so let's go!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are fighting dreamers, aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting dreamers, don't care what people think
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting dreamers, follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here Right now
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna get the fire!
Right here Right now
音を立てず忍び寄る影が いつも僕らを惑わせる
Creeping soundless shadows always puzzling us
有言実行大きな風がうねりを上げて吹き荒れる
Big short burst of wind feels like a hurricane
かざした鋭い刀で 己の未来切り開け!
Raise a blade to cut through your future!
保証なんてどこにもないさ なあそうだろう!?
There's no guarantee anywhere, right?!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are fighting dreamers, aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting dreamers, don't care what people think
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting dreamers, follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers don't care what people think
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and get the fire!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and get the fire!
険しい修羅の道の中 ひとりの地図を広げて何処へ行く?
Down a difficult road filled with endless struggles...
極彩色のカラスが それを奪い取って破り捨てた
A wise crow comes along to tear up the map
さあ心の目 見開いて しかと今を見極めろ!
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth!
失うモノなんてないさ いざ参らん!
There's nothing to lose, so let's go!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers don't care what people think
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
We are Fighting Dreamers 全てを巻き込み
We are Fighting Dreamers involving everything
Fighting Dreamers 志高く
Fighting Dreamers with high aspirations
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
心ざし高く
With high aspirations...
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and get the fire!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and get the fire!
We are Fighting Dreamers この仲間達と
We are Fighting Dreamers with these comrades
Fighting Dreamers 全てを巻き込み
Fighting Dreamers involving everything
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and get the fire!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and get the fire!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and get the fire!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and get the fire!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and get the fire!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and get the fire!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
We're gonna do it and get the fire!
ガラス玉ひとつ 落とされた
A single glass ball fell
追いかけてもうひとつ落っこちた
When I went after it, another dropped
ひとつ分の陽だまりに ひとつだけ残ってる
There's only enough sun for one left
心臓が始まった時 嫌でも場所を取る
As soon as your heart starts beating, you take up space
奪われない様に 守り続けてる
And you protect that space so no one else can take it
汚さずに保ってきた手でも 汚れて見えた
The hands I'd kept clean now look dirty
記憶を疑う 前に 記憶に疑われてる
Before I can doubt my memories, my memories are doubting me
必ず 僕らは 出会うだろう 同じ鼓動の音を目印にして
We'll meet for sure, using our heartbeats as signs
ここに居るよ いつだって呼んでるから
I'm here, and I'm always calling you
くたびれた理由が 重なって揺れる時
When the tired old reasons pile up and start to sway
生まれた意味を知る
That's when you know the reason you were born
存在する 限り 仕方ないから 場所を取る
As long as life exists, we take up space
ひとつ分の陽だまりに ふたつはちょっと入れない
Two can't fit in just enough sun for one
ガラス玉ひとつ 落とされた 落ちた 時 何か 弾き出した
A single glass ball fell, and something shot out
奪い取った 場所で 光を 浴びた
It bathed in the light in the spot it stole
数えた 足跡 など 気づけば 数字でしかない
Counting footprints until they're just numbers...
初めて 僕らは 出会うだろう 同じ悲鳴の旗を目印にして
We'll meet for the first time using our screaming flags
忘れないで いつだって 呼んでるから
Don't forget, I'm always calling you
重ねた理由を 二人で 埋める 時
When we bury all the piled up reasons
約束が 交わされる
That's when we'll make a promise
汚れた 手と手 で 触れ合って 形 が 解れる
Our dirty hands will touch and we'll know its shape
ここに 居るよ 確実に 触れるよ
I'm here, and I can touch you
一人分の陽だまりに 僕らは居る
We're both here in this sun for one
忘れないで いつだって 呼んでるから 同じガラス玉の内側の方から
Calling you from the inside of the same glass ball
そうさ 必ず 僕らは出会うだろう 沈めた理由に十字架を立てる 時
We'll meet for sure when you build a cross on the reasons
約束は果たされる
The promise will be fulfilled
初めて 僕らは出会うだろう
We'll meet for the first time
同じ悲鳴の旗を目印にして
Using our screaming flags as signs
ここにいるよ いつだって呼んでるから
I'm here, and I'm always calling you
重ねた理由を 二人で踏める時
When we step on and bury the piled reasons
約束が交わされる
The promise is made
鏡なんだ 僕ら 互いに それぞれの カルマを 映す為の
We're mirrors reflecting each other's karma
汚れた 手と手 で 触れ合って 形 が 解れる
Our dirty hands touch and the shape dissolves
ここに居るよ 確実に触れるよ
I'm here, and I can touch you
一人分の陽だまりに 僕らは居る
We're both here in this sun that's only for one
忘れないで いつだって 呼んでるから 同じガラス玉の内側の方から
Always calling from inside the same glass ball
そうさ 必ず 僕らは出会うだろう 沈めた理由に十字架を立てる 時
We'll meet for sure when a cross is built on the reasons
約束は果たされる 確かに触れるよ
The promise will be fulfilled, and we'll become one
初めて僕らは出会うだろう
We'll meet for the first time
同じ悲鳴の旗を目印にして
Using our screaming flags as signs
そうさ必ず僕らは出会うだろう 同じカルマの反対側の方から
We'll meet for sure from the other side of karma
沈めた理由に十字架を立てる時
When we step on and bury the buried reasons
約束は果たされる 誓うよ
The promise is made and we become one
僕らはひとつになる
We will become one
今日も君は 信じることを
Can you wake up today too...
忘れずに目覚められていますか？
...without forgetting to believe?
時が経つと自分さえも信じれなくなる時代のようで
Like an era where as time passes, you can't even believe in yourself,
自分では気付かないのが
Not realizing it yourself
この症状の特徴で
Is the characteristic of this symptom,
唯一ある予防法は…
And the only preventive method...
「自分にウソだけゃつかない事」
...is 'never telling lies to yourself'.
忘れてたまるもんかよ！！
As if I'd ever forget that!!
僕がボクじゃなくなったら
If I stopped being who I am,
たとえ生きてたって生きてる意味すら見つからんだろ
Even if I were alive, I wouldn't find any meaning in living.
声にならない叫びは僕が声を枯らして叫んで歌って
My unspoken screams—I'll strain my voice, shouting and singing,
伝わるまでわめいて 届くまで止めない！！
Ranting until it gets across, never stopping until it reaches you!!
今日も地球は回り続ける
Today too, the earth keeps spinning.
誰が泣いてても怒っても止まらず
Regardless of who cries or gets angry, it never stops.
ためしに僕が…風邪をひいてももちろん止まることなんてねぇわ
Just to test, even if I catch a cold, of course it won't stop!!
人生も同じように止まることはなく進むから そうさ今日も人はお手のシワとシワをあわせの！
Life is the same, moving forward without stopping, so today too, people clap their hands together!
終わらせちまうことなんかけして誰にだってできんだろ？！
Anyone can put an end to things, right?!
たとえ終わっちまったって次のスタートすぐきれんだろ？！
Even if it ends, you can start right over right away, right?!
今キミがもうキセキも底上げさせてしまえば
If you elevate your own miracles right now,
もうその時点でそのキセキは君にとっちゃ必然のお仲間さ！！
At that very point, those miracles become your inevitable companions!!
WOW…
WOW...
なんかあいだめダメと言われようが
No matter how much they tell you 'no, no',
実際問題そんなん関係なくて
In reality, that has nothing to do with it.
今自分自身必要なものたくわえてそろえとけよ！！
Right now, gather and prepare whatever you personally need!!
なぁそうだろ？！ まだまだ時間はまだあんぞ！！
Right? There's still plenty of time!!
先見の明 今はとぎすまして 主人公は一人だけ！！
Sharpen your foresight right now, you are the only protagonist!!
自分の物語のはじまり！！
The beginning of your own story!!
もうすぐ時計は6時
Soon the clock will strike 6,
もうそこに一番星
And the first star is right there.
影を踏んで 夜に紛れたくなる帰り道
Stepping on shadows, wanting to get lost in the night on the way home.
どんなに探してみても一つしかない星
No matter how much I search, there's only that single star.
何億光年 離れたところからあんなに輝く
Shining so brightly from hundreds of millions of light-years away.
もうすぐ時計は6時
The clock is almost at 6,
もうそこに一番星
and the first star is right there.
影を踏んで 夜に紛れたくなる帰り道
On my way home, stepping on shadows, wanting to blend into the night.
どんなに探してみても
No matter how much I search,
一つしかない星
there's only one star.
何億光年 離れたところからあんなに輝く
Glowing so bright from hundreds of millions of light-years away.
いいな
Must be nice,
君はみんなから愛されて
everyone loves you.
「いいや 僕は ずっと一人きりさ」
"Nah, I'm always all by myself."
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
星降る夜 一瞬の願い事
a fleeting wish on a starry night.
きらめいて ゆらめいて 震えているシグナル
Twinkling, shimmering, a trembling signal.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
空見上げて 指を差せるようなつないだ線
pointing up at the sky, connected lines
解けないで
that won't come undone,
僕がどんなに眩しくても
no matter how dazzling I am.
もうすぐ時計は8時
The clock is almost at 8,
夜空に満天の星
the night sky is full of stars.
何億光年 離れたところにはもうないかもしれない
They might not even be there anymore, millions of light-years away.
月が綺麗で 泣きそうになるのは いつ日にか別れが来るから
The moon is so beautiful, I feel like crying because one day a farewell will come.
君と集まって 星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
流れ星みたいな流れるひとりごと
a monologue flowing like a shooting star.
消えていく残像は 真夜中のプリズム
The fading afterimage is a midnight prism.
君と集まって 星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
切なる願い 誰かに届いたら 変われるかな 夜の淵をなぞるようなこんな僕でも
If my earnest wish reaches someone, can I change, even a person like me tracing the edge of the night?
遥か彼方 僕らは出会ってしまった カルマだから 何度も出会ってしまうよ
Far away, we ended up meeting. Because it's karma, we keep meeting again and again.
雲の隙間で 君と集まって 星座になれたら
In the gaps of the clouds, if I could gather with you and become a constellation,
夜空広げて 描こう絵空事
spreading the night sky, let's paint an illusion.
暗闇を照らすような 満月じゃなくても
Even if it's not a full moon illuminating the darkness,
遥か彼方 僕らは出会ってしまった
Far away, we ended up meeting.
カルマだから 何度も出会ってしまうよ
Because it's karma, we keep meeting again and again.
雲の隙間で
In the gaps of the clouds...
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
夜広げて 描こう絵空事
spreading the night sky, let's paint an illusion.
暗闇を照らすような 満月じゃなくても
Even if it's not a full moon illuminating the darkness,
だから 集まって 星座になりたい
That's why I want to gather and become a constellation,
色とりどりの光 放つような
like releasing multicolored light.
つないだ線 ほどけないよ
The connected lines won't come undone,
君がどんなに眩しくても
no matter how dazzling you are.
はい、ということで！
Yes, so!
Fesじゃーん！
It's a Fes!
イェーイ！
Yay!
緊張したー！
I was so nervous!
めっちゃ緊張したね！
Super nervous!
よかったよかった！
Glad it went well!
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
緊張したよねー
I was so nervous~
ちょっと待ってね
Hold on a second
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
あの、FGでね、ずっとバンドがやりたいって思っていたので
Um, I've always wanted to be in a band in FG,
ま、今日はちょっと、エアバンドなんですけれどもね
well, today it's an air band, but still,
みんなで星座になれたら、叶えていただけましたー！
if we could become a constellation together, my wish came true!
じゃあ一回、自己紹介しとくか。
Let's do a self-introduction first.
オッケー！
Okay!
じゃあリッチャンから、いつも通りのやつお願いしまーす！
Then Ritchan, please do your usual thing!
はーい！
Okay!
世界で一番お姫様に愛でられるのエンジェハース！
The most adored princess in the world, Angel Heath!
リッチゃーんって呼んでください！
Please call me Ritchan!
ボンボンボンボン
(Bass sounds)
右の低音もかっこいいよりょな
The low bass notes are so cool too!
りっちゃん お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday, Ritchan!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
そして、二コタンが来た！ホラブデバイズフロッグローの
And Nikotan is here! From Horabudeice Frogrow...
キーボード担当！
Keyboardist!
新潟、ありがとう！
Niigata, thank you!
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい、そしていつも充電足りてる？ホライブデバイズフロッグローの、ドラム担当！
And, are you always charged enough? From Horibudeice Frogrow, the drummer!
りんりんだよ！
Rinrin here!
千早 お誕生日おめでとう！
Chihaya, happy birthday!
おめでとうー！
Congratulations!
そして？
And?
あ、はい！
Ah, yes!
ホライブデバイズフロッグローの...
From Horibudeice Frogrow...
みんなキラキラなキラキラビビでーす！
Everyone, sparkling, sparkling Bibi here!
あ、忘れてた。ビビはギター担当と…
Oh, I forgot. Bibi is in charge of guitar...
ドゥルルルル〜 じゃんじゃん
Drurururu~ Jan-jan!
そうね。足引いてるよ。
That's right. You're dragging us down.
千ハ、お誕生日おめでとう！ありがとー！
Chihaya, happy birthday! Thank you so much!
ありがとう！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
いや、ということでみんな来てくれて、ありがとう！
Yeah, so thank you everyone for coming!
え、なんかいいお知らせがあるんじゃないの？
Eh, isn't there some good news?
なんと！トレンド1位になったらしい！
What do you know? It apparently reached #1 on trending!
トレンド1位！やったー！嬉しい！
#1 on trending! Yay! I'm so happy!
なんか今までね、トレンド2文字だから、
Up until now, trending was just two characters,
あのトレンドに乗らねえのよ。
so it wouldn't catch on trending.
ああ、なるほどね。そうそう。
Ah, I see. That's right.
誕生日に嬉しい、あのプレゼントをいただきまして、本当にありがとうございます。
To receive such a happy birthday present, thank you so much.
いっぱいツイートしてくれたんだね。ありがとう！もっとしてね！
You tweeted so much. Thank you! Tweet even more!
正座になりたら披露しましたけど、皆さんどうでしたか？
We performed while sitting, but how was it, everyone?
楽しかった！楽しかった！楽しかった！
It was fun! Fun! Fun!
ドラムを叩きたくなりました。
I wanted to play the drums.
ドラムね、似合ってるんだよね。そうなんです、実は。
Drums suit you so well. That's right, actually.
だから、いつかFGバンドをね結成したいの。
So someday I want to form an FG band.
絶対できる！できる！結成したいの。
Definitely possible! We can! I want to form it.
今回はエアバンドだったのね、ニコタンにね、キーボードを担当していただいたんですけど。
Nikotan was in charge of the keyboard this time.
うん、ね、すごかったでしょ？
Yeah, right? It was amazing, wasn't it?
すごかった本当に。全身で引いてたもんね。
It really was. She was playing with her whole body.
全身で引いてくれてたね。すごい。すごかった。もう全部やるよ、マジで。
She played with her whole body. Amazing. I'll do everything!
いや、できひん、できひん。1歩も触れずにね。
No, you can't, you can't, without even taking a step.
みんな楽しん、ニコタンもすごい楽しかったし、みんなも楽しそうにしてくれてとっても嬉しかったです。
Everyone had fun, Nikotan too, and I was so happy.
いつか実現させましょう。
Let's make it happen someday.
絶対しよう！絶対しよう！しよーよー！
Definitely let's do it! Let's do it!
そんな時はみんな今回の楽器でいいんですか？
Are you all okay with the same instruments?
え、あれ、聞こえてる、待って。違う、楽器やりたいいって。
Wait, I said I want to play an instrument!
歌う、歌う！歌うじゃなくて、ダメ！歌いたい！
Not singing, no! I want to sing!
だって、みんなね、足の怪我直ったとこじゃん。
Because everyone's foot injuries just healed.
え、ニコタンはさ、やるとしたら何の楽器やりたい？
Nikotan, what instrument would you want to play?
いや、だって何んでもいいよ。もう出まくってるよ、もうね。
Anything is fine. I'm already all over the place!
ギター、今ギター、ギター、ドラムベースがいるんだけど。
Right now there's guitar, guitar, drums, and bass.
そしたらでもやっぱキーボードしか無いよね。
Then after all, there's only keyboard, right?
バイオリン、これがあるやん。これがあるやん。打楽器、打楽器は？トライアングルとか。
Violin, there's this. Percussion like a triangle?
トライアングルとか。でも、ビビもトライアングル、タンバリンとか、いいんじゃない？
Triangle, tambourine, wouldn't that be good?
全員でなんか打楽器バンド。
A percussion band with everyone.
いいじゃん、ビビはそれでいいのか？いや、全然違うタイプでやるから、やめろ、それ。
That's fine, is Bibi okay with just that?
え、でも、そういうのもやってみたい、楽しそう。
Eh, but I'd like to try that too, sounds fun.
確かに。FGの企画とかでやったりするのね、確かに。
True, doing it for FG projects, true.
やろう、やろう！やりましょう！
Let's do it, let's do it!
本当に今日はね、長い時間リハーサルから付き合ってもらって、本当にありがとう！
Thank you for sticking with us from rehearsal today!
おめでとう！ありがとう！
Congratulations! Thank you!
なんかこの、これは何でも、じゃあが何でもします券を皆様に。
This "we'll do anything ticket" to everyone.
何でもって言ったの？何でもって言ったの？
Did you say "anything"?
何でもいいよ。
Anything is fine.
一人1枚？
One per person?
一人1枚！やったー！
One per person! Yay!
取り消し！取り消し券出し！取り消し券出しない！
Cancellation! Don't issue cancellation tickets!
美味しいご飯ごちそうさま！
Thanks for the delicious meal!
それはもうもちろん全員におごらせていただきますので。
Of course I'll treat everyone.
今日もお弁当豪華だったね。
Today's bento boxes were luxurious, weren't they?
お弁当めっちゃ豪華だった！テンション爆発しました！
The bentos were super luxurious! Our excitement exploded!
よかったら喜んでいただいて。まだあるので持って帰ってください。
I'm glad you were pleased. Please take some home.
はい、ではね、そろそろ次の曲に行きたいと思います。
I think it's almost time for the next song.
みんなも見ててくれるかな？バッチリ見てね！
Will everyone be watching? Watch properly!
では、ライブ見てくれてるみんなもまだまだ盛り上がっていってくださいねー！イエーイ！
Everyone watching the live, keep getting hyped! Yay!
まだコメント欄はなんでもって言ってる。
The chat is still saying "anything".
帰ろうとしないで！リスナーさんたちにはなんでもしないですけど、FGちゃんたちにはなんでもしてあげたい気持ちでね。
Don't try to go home! We want to do anything for the FG-chans.
もちろんそれぐらいの愛があるから、気持ちだけじゃなくてね。
Because there's that much love, not just in feelings.
やばいよ、みんな。全部叶えてくれるからみんな！ありがとう！
This is crazy, they're granting everything! Thank you!
おれも一緒にいこう。しゅしゅしゅしゅしゅしゅ〜
I'll go with you too. Shu shu shu...
あの日見渡した渚を 今も思い出すんだ
I can still remember the shore we saw that day...
砂の上に刻んだ言葉 君の後ろ姿
The words we wrote in the sand... The sight of you as you turned away
寄り返す波が足元をよぎり何かをさらう 夕凪の中日暮れだけが通り過ぎていく
The waves ebb and flow, and twilight passes me by
パッと光って咲いた花火を見ていた きっとまだ終わらない夏が
We watched fireworks blooming; this summer is far from over
あの日見わたした渚を
The beach we looked out at that day,
今も思い出すんだ
I still remember it now.
砂の上に刻んだ言葉
Words carved into the sand,
君の後ろ姿
Your retreating figure.
寄り添う波が足元をよぎり 何かをさらう
Nuzzling waves brush past our feet, washing something away.
夕凪の中 日暮れだけが通り過ぎてゆく
In the evening calm, only twilight passes us by.
パッと光って咲いた 花火を見ていた
I was watching the fireworks flash and bloom.
きっとまだ終わらない夏が
Surely a summer that won't end yet
曖昧な心を解かして繋いだ
melted and tied our ambiguous hearts together.
この夜が続いて欲しかった
I wanted this night to keep going.
あと何回君と同じ
Wondering how many more times
花火を見られるかなって
I can see these fireworks with you,
あと何度君と同じ 花火を見られるかなって
Wondering how many more times I can see these fireworks with you,
笑う顔に何ができるだろうか
what can I do for that smiling face?
傷つくこと 喜ぶこと
Hurting and rejoicing,
繰り返す波と情動 焦燥 最終列車の音
repeating waves and emotions, impatience, the sound of the last train.
何度でも言葉にして君を呼ぶよ
I'll call out your name in words no matter how many times,
波間を選び もう一度
choosing the space between waves, once more.
もう二度と 悲しまずに済むように
So that we never have to feel sad again,
紡ぐように…
like weaving a thread...
パッと息をのめば 消えてしまいそうな光が
If I gasp, the light that seems ready to vanish
きっとまだ胸に住んでいた
was surely still dwelling in my chest.
手を伸ばせば触れた あったかい未来は
The warm future I could touch if I reached out
密かにふたりをみていた
was quietly watching the two of us.
パッと花火が 夜に咲いた
Fireworks suddenly bloomed in the night.
静かに消えた 離さないで
Fading quietly, don't let go.
もう少しだけ このままで
Just a little bit longer, stay like this.
あの日見わたした渚を 今も思い出すんだ
I still remember the beach we looked out at that day.
砂の上に刻んだ言葉 君の後ろ姿
Words carved in the sand, your retreating figure.
パッと光って咲いた 花火を見ていた
I was watching the fireworks flash and bloom.
きっとまだ終わらない夏が
Surely a summer that won't end yet
曖昧な心を解かして繋いだ
melted and tied our ambiguous hearts together.
この夜が続いて欲しかった
I wanted this night to keep going.
ラララ…
La la la...
思い違いは 空のかなた
Misunderstandings are beyond the sky,
さよならだけの 人生か
Is this a life of nothing but goodbyes?
ほんの少しの 未来は 見えたのに
Though a glimpse of the future was visible...
ほんの少しの未来は見えたのに さよならなんだ
A tiny bit of the future was in sight, but it's goodbye.
昔住んでた小さな部屋は
The small room where I once lived
今は誰かが住んでんだ
is now lived in by someone else.
君に言われた ひどい言葉も
The harsh words you said to me
無駄な気がした 毎日も
and the days that felt so wasted—
あの時こうしてれば あの日に戻れれば
If I had done this then, if I could go back to that day,
あの頃の僕にはもう戻れないよ
I can never return to who I was back then.
たとえばゆるい幸せが だらっと続いたとする
Suppose a casual happiness continued lazily;
きっと悪い種が芽を出して もうさよならなんだ
a bad seed would surely sprout, and it would be goodbye.
寒い冬の冷たいた缶コーヒーと
A cold canned coffee from the chilly winter
虹色の長いマフラー
and a long, rainbow-colored scarf.
小走りで路地裏を抜けて
Hurrying through the back alleys,
思い出してみる
I try to remember.
たとえばゆるい幸せが だらっと続いたとする
Suppose a casual happiness continued lazily;
きっと悪い種が芽を出して もうさよならなんだ
a bad seed would surely sprout, and it would be goodbye.
なんだ なんた なんた…
What is it, what is it...
さよなら、それもいいさ
Goodbye, that's fine too.
どこかで元気にやれよ
Do well wherever you are.
さよなら、僕もどうにかやるさ
Goodbye, I'll somehow manage too.
さよなら、そうするよ
Goodbye, I'll do just that.
お疲れ様！はい、ということで、ソラニンをお送りしました。いかがだったでしょうか。
Good work! So, that was "Solanin." How was it?
いや、あの、見覚えがある方もいらっしゃるのではないでしょうか。
Well, I suppose there are some of you who might recognize it.
これ、あの、初めて見る方もいらっしゃるかなと思うんですが、あの、FGの3Dお披露目の時にも、えっと、ギターの弾き語りをお披露目させていただいたんですけれども、その時よりもレベルアップできていたでしょうか。
Some of you might be seeing this for the first time, but I also performed an acoustic guitar cover during my FG 3D debut showcase. I wonder if I've leveled up since then.
初めて、たぶん最初の頃に練習したのがソラニンで、そこからずっとちゃんとできた姿をみんなに見せたかったのでこの曲を選びました。
Solanin was probably one of the first songs I practiced, and I always wanted to show everyone how much I'd improved, which is why I chose it.
そしてですね、ギター千花の音だけじゃなくてもう1本ソロとかベースがあったと思うんですが、それはですね、千花のギターの先生に一緒に弾いていただきました！
And you know, besides Chihaya's guitar, there was also a solo and bass part—that was actually played together with Chihaya's guitar teacher!
なんかレッスンの時にセッションしてたら「え、めちゃくちゃかっこよくね？」ってなって、先生もよかったら一緒に弾いてくれませんかって言って、一緒にね、弾いていただきました。ありがとうございました！
During a lesson, we were jamming and thought, "Whoa, this sounds so cool!" So I asked the teacher if they'd play along with me, and they did. Thank you so much!
ということでね、いったんここまでの振り返りをしていこうかなと思いますよ。まず最初はゲストパートで1曲目が...
So, with that, let's look back at what we've done so far. First up was the guest part, and the first song was...
58で5！
58 and 5!
ファイト、リマは…しましてどうですか、
Fight, Rima... How was that?
やっぱ1曲目はぶち上げていきたいなと思って、
I really wanted to hype things up right from the first song,
2曲目はね、めっちゃ盛り上がる曲を選びました！
so I chose a super hype song for the second one!
もう先輩たちのね、ぶち上げがかっこよくて、「じゃあもう頑張るぞ！」ってなったので
The seniors' hype was so cool, and it made me think, "Alright, I'll do my best!"
楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいです。
I hope you all enjoyed it.
そして2曲目はTowa様と「カルマ」を歌いました！
And for the second song, I sang "Karma" with Towa-sama!
やっぱTowa様の低音が大好きなので、ちょっと無理を言って原曲キーでね、すごい低い中、一緒に歌っていただけました！
I just love Towa-sama's low voice, so I asked to keep the original key, and we got to sing it together in that super low range!
Towa様ありがとうございました！めっちゃかっこよかったです。
Thank you so much, Towa-sama! It was super cool.
そして3曲目がルイ先輩と「自分ロック」！
And the third song was "Jibun Rock" with Lui-senpai!
いや、やっぱルイ先輩かっこよくない！？やばいんですけど。
I mean, isn't Lui-senpai just so cool!? It's insane.
あの、本当にルイ先輩のかっこいい、ちょっとこうガナリの利いた、エッジの利いた声で歌いたいなと思ってこの曲を選びました。超かっこよかったよね！
I chose this song because I really wanted to sing with Lui-senpai's cool, gritty, edgy voice. It was super cool, right?
そして6曲目が揃いになれたら、さっきね、フッシーちゃんたちと一緒にわいわいしたセトリになれたらって、
And for the 6th song, I wanted a setlist where we could all get together and have fun chatting like with Fussy-chan and the others,
7曲目激エモの「にゃんちゃんおかゆ先輩」との打ち上げ花火どうでしたか？
and how was the super emotional fireworks with "Nyan-chan Okayu-senpai" for the 7th song?
もうマジ、あの、本当に、おにぎりのみんなには申し訳ないんですけど、あの瞬間はもうガチで、おかゆ先輩の彼氏のつもりでもう、ってやってしまいました。
Seriously, I'm really sorry to all the Onigiri members, but in that moment I honestly acted like I was Okayu-senpai's boyfriend, haha.
もうあの、もう最高でした！ありがとうございました、本当に。あの、もうお返しします、すいません、ありがとうございました。
It was just the absolute best! Thank you so much. Uh, I'll give her back now, sorry, thank you!
というね、エモエモな、ぱっとかっこいいからエモまでのパートがありましたが、楽しんでいただけてますかー！？
So we had a section going from cool to super emotional—did you all enjoy it?!
ちょっとコメント見てみようかな。
Let's check the comments for a second.
「え、エモすぎた」「泣いた」「え、分かる！分かる！めっちゃエモいよね！」
"'So emotional,' 'I cried,' 'I know, right?! It's super emotional!'"
チハもなんかやりながら、「エモすぎるこれ」と思ってやってましたよー！
Even while doing it, I was thinking, "This is too emotional!" and doing it!
ありがとう！めっちゃよかったよね！
Thank you! It was really great, right?
さあ、ということでね、ちょっとあのチハヤ、あの、喋らせると、あの、喋りすぎてしまうので、ちょっと次のパートに行きたいんですが、
Now, with that said, if you let Chihaya talk, she'll just keep going on and on, so I want to move on to the next part,
ここからは嬉しいお知らせとなります！
and from here we have some happy announcements!
鈴代千葉誕生日記念2026グッズ販売のお知らせとなります！生誕グッズが出るぞ！こちらをご覧ください、どん！
It's the announcement for the Chihaya Rindo Birthday Anniversary 2026 merch! Birthday merch is coming out! Please take a look here, ta-da!
はーい！もりだくさんですねー！
Yay! There's so much stuff!
イラストは鳥得の先生に、ままに、描いていただきました！ありがとうございます！ギターをね、引いてるライブのワンシーンをイメージして描いていただきました。いや、めっちゃかっこいいよね！
The illustration was drawn by Toridome-sensei, my mama! Thank you so much! They drew it imagining a live performance scene where I'm playing the guitar. It's just super cool, right?
それではね、詳細を見ていきましょう！まずは、こちら！
Now then, let's take a look at the details! First up is this!
鈴代千葉誕生日記念フェスTシャツ2026でございます！
It's the Chihaya Rindo Birthday Fest T-Shirt 2026!
キービジュアルのイラスト全身を使用した、かっこかわいいTシャツです！
It's a cool yet cute T-shirt featuring the full-body key visual illustration!
バンドTシャツっぽくしたくて、ちょっとロゴとかイカつい感じにしてもらったので、
I wanted it to look like a band T-shirt, so we made the logo and vibe a bit edgy and badass,
ぜひぜひライブにとか、日常でも着てもらえたら嬉しいです！
so I'd be super happy if you wear it to live shows or even in daily life!
続いては、こちら！ピックケースキーホルダーです！
Next up is this! The pick case keyholder!
お気に入りのピックを入れて、おしゃれに持ち運べるキーホルダーです。
It's a stylish keyholder where you can put your favorite guitar pick and carry it around.
キーホルダーがメインで、3枚のピックは付属品としてついています！ピックケースホルダーにはピックが1枚入る仕様です。
The keyholder is the main item, and three picks come as accessories! The case is designed to hold one pick inside.
あの、今回のために書いたサインとかロゴとか、あとはフラットアウトっていうロゴ、今回のあのタイトルにもなってるフラットアウトのロゴが描かれているピックがセットになっています！
It comes with a set of picks featuring signatures and logos drawn just for this occasion, as well as the "Flat Out" logo featured in our title!
続いては、こちら！ちととお出かけバッグです！
Next up is this! The Chito Outing Bag!
前にポーチがついていて、前のポーチをひっくり返すと中身を見せて推しバッグにチェンジできる、ちょっとね、機能性のあるバッグ、斜めがけのバッグになっています！
It has a pouch on the front, and by flipping the front pouch inside out, you can show off your oshi items and turn it into a clear display bag—a super functional crossbody bag!
いろんなところこれでお出かけしてください！
Please take it out with you everywhere!
そして、続いては、こちら！どこでもふぐたろうティッシュカバー！ふんわりとした質感のふぐたろうモチーフのティッシュカバーです！
And next up is this! The "Anywhere Fugutaro Tissue Cover"! It's a fluffy-textured tissue cover featuring the Fugutaro motif!
え、かわいいよね！おうちでも、車でも、職場でもふぐたろうを連れていけます！
Isn't it cute?! You can take Fugutaro with you at home, in the car, or even at work!
そして続いては、こちら！シチュエーションボイスです！
And next up is this! The situational voice!
タイトルは「ライブリハーサルボイス」。ライブ前のリハーサルで「ドキドキ、緊張してる…」チハのシチュエーションボイスになっておりますので、ドキドキの緊張感をぜひ聴きに来てください！
The title is "Live Rehearsal Voice". It's a situational voice of Chihaya being all nervous and excited during rehearsal before the live, so please come listen to the nervous tension!
そしてフルセット購入特典もあります！こちら！直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードです！
And there's also a full-set purchase bonus! Here it is! A instax-style bromide card with a handwritten signature and foil-stamped duplicated message!
全部ね、直筆でチハヤがサインを書きますのでね、ぜひぜひフルセットで購入していただけるととっても嬉しいです！
Chihaya will handwrite signatures on every single one, so I'd be super happy if you purchase the full set!
そして特典ボイス、タイトルは「ライブ後、君と」になります！先ほどのね、ボイスと合わせて聴くと、またよりエモさを感じられるのではないかなと思うので、ぜひこちらも聴いてみてください！
And the bonus voice is titled "After the Live, with You"! If you listen to it along with the previous voice, I think you'll feel even more emotional, so definitely check this one out too!
改めて、フルセットはこちらになります！やばね、これ全部、Tシャツ着て、バッグ持って、キーホルダーつけて、え、ふぐたろう持って、どこでも行けるチハヤセット、チハヤセットなので、
To recap, here is the full set! Seriously, wearing the T-shirt, carrying the bag, putting on the keyholder, and bringing Fugutaro... it's the ultimate "Go Anywhere Chihaya Set"!
ま、買うならフルセットの方がいいよね！21時、この後21時カートオープンとなりますので、数量限定ではないのでぜひね、あの、ゆっくり購入していただけるととっても嬉しいです！よろしくお
So if you're gonna buy, the full set is definitely the way to go! The cart opens at 21:00 just after this, and it's not quantity-limited, so please take your time purchasing! Thank you so much!
お願いします。
Please enjoy.
そして皆様待望のおしらせがございます！
And everyone, we have a long-awaited announcement!
こちら、なんと！
Here, what's more!
輪堂千速ソロとしては初めてのオリジナル曲「Flatout」が、この後24時、7月9日木曜日の0時にデジタルリリースされます！
Chihaya Rindo's first solo original song "Flatout" will be digitally released tonight at midnight!
やったー！
Yay!
今回のライブのタイトルにもなっている「Flatout」はオリジナル曲のタイトルでございました！
"Flatout," which is also the title of this live concert, is the title of the original song!
この配信が終わった後にMVが公開されますので、そちらもぜひお楽しみに！
The MV will be released after this stream ends, so please look forward to that as well!
概要欄にそのうち多分リンクが貼られたり貼られなかったりすると思うのでそちらもチェックしてみてください。
I think a link will probably be posted in the description box, so please check that out too.
新曲この後やっぱ早速聴きたいですよね？この後披露するので絶対に聴いてください！
You definitely want to listen to the new song right away after this, right? Be sure to listen!
最後まで、最後までねチャンネルはそのまま見ていって下さいね！
Until the very end, please keep watching the channel just like this!
以上は輪堂千速生誕祭2026のグッズ情報とリリース情報でした！
That concludes the goods and release info for Chihaya Rindo's 2026 Birthday Festival!
みんな勝手にサブスクでも聞いてね！
Everyone, be sure to stream it on subscriptions on your own too!
はーい！
Right!
ということで怒涛のおしらせコーナーでした！ここからいよいよライブもクライマックスです！
So that was our whirlwind announcement corner! The live finally reaches its climax!
でもまだまだあります！盛り上がる準備できてますか？最後一緒にぶち上げていこうね！
Are you ready to get hyped? Let's go out with a bang together!
では準備してきます。
Well then, I'll go get ready.
あお！そのチャンネルはそのままに！
Oh! Keep that channel right as it is!
ワタリドリ 作詞・作曲：川上洋平
[Song: Wataridori | Lyrics & Music: Yohei Kawakami]
i wanna fly so high
yeah, i know my wings are dried
「羽仰げば」って人は言う
People say, "If you look up at wings,"
その向こうにあるは無情
what lies beyond is heartlessness.
飛べる者 落ちる者
Those who can fly, those who fall—
誰も見てない 気にも留めない それでも飛び続けた
no one watches, no one cares, yet I kept flying anyway.
傷ついた言葉乗せ 運びたいから
Because I want to carry and deliver words filled with scars,
追いかけて 届くよう
chasing after them so they will reach you.
僕等 一心に 羽ばたいて
We flap our wings with all our hearts,
問いかけて 嘆いた夜
questioning and lamenting the night.
故郷は 一層 輝いて
Our hometown shines even brighter,
ワタリドリの様に今 旅に発つよ
and now, like migrating birds, I set off on a journey.
ありもしないストーリーを 描いてみせるよ
I'll show you I can draw a story that doesn't even exist.
i wanna fly so far away with my guitar
「一人じゃない」って人々は歌う
People sing, "You're not alone."
間違いじゃない 理想論でもない
It's not a mistake, nor is it idealism.
ただ頼って生きたくはない
I don't want to live just by leaning on others.
誰も聴いてない 気にも留めない それでも歌い続けた
No one listens, no one cares, yet I kept on singing anyway.
傷ついたあなたを笑わせたいから
Because I want to make you smile, you who have been hurt,
追い風 届けるよ
I will deliver a tailwind to you.
僕等 一心に 羽ばたいて
We flap our wings with all our hearts,
遠い過去を背負ってた
carrying a distant past on our backs,
あなたを未来へ運ぶよ
carrying you into the future.
ワタリドリの様に今 群れをなして
Like migrating birds, we flock together now,
大それた四重奏を 奏で終える日まで
until the day an outrageous quartet finishes playing.
all this time we come and we grow, and now it's time that we should go
but we both know that this is for sure, it's not the end of the world
well, see you one day
追いかけて 届くよう
Chasing after them so they will reach you,
僕等 一心に 羽ばたいて
we flap our wings with all our hearts.
問いかけて 嘆いた夜
Questioning and lamenting the night,
朝焼け色に染まっていく
we become dyed in the colors of sunrise.
ワタリドリの様にいつか 舞い戻るよ
Someday, like migrating birds, I'll dance back.
ありもしないストーリーを いつかまた会う日まで
A story that doesn't exist—until the day we meet again.
i wanna fly so high, yeah, i know my wings are dried
「翼仰げば」って人は云う その向こうにあるは無情
People say, "Look up at the wings," but beyond that is heartlessness.
飛べる者 落ちる者 誰も見てない 気にも留めない
Those who can fly, those who fall—no one watches, no one cares.
それでも飛び続けた 傷付いた言葉乗せ運びたいから
Yet I kept on flying, because I want to carry wounded words.
追いかけて届くよう 僕等一心に羽ばたいて
So that I can chase and reach you, we flap our wings as one.
問いかけて嘆いていた夜 故郷は一層輝いて
On nights when I questioned and grieved, my homeland shone all the brighter.
ワタリドリの様に今旅に発つよ ありもしないストーリーを描いてみせるよ
Now I set off on a journey like a migratory bird, to sketch a story that doesn't exist.
i wanna fly so far away with my guitar
「一人じゃない」って人々は歌う 間違いじゃない 理想論でもない
People sing, "You're not alone." It's not a mistake, nor is it mere idealism.
ただ頼って生きていきたいわけはない 誰も聴いていない 気にも留めない
It's not that I just want to live by relying on others. No one is listening, no one cares.
それでも歌い続けた 傷付いたあなたを笑わせたいから
Yet I kept on singing, because I want to make you, who were hurt, smile.
追い風届けるよ 僕等一心に羽ばたいて
I'll deliver a tailwind to you, as we flap our wings as one.
遠い過去を背負ってた あなたを未来へ運ぶよ
I will carry you, burdened with a distant past, into the future.
ワタリドリの様に今群れをなして 大それた四重奏を奏で終わる日まで
Now flocking together like migratory birds, until the day we finish playing our grand quartet.
all this time we come and we grow and now it's time that we should go
well, see you one day
Shiny Smily Story (2022 ver.)
[Song: Shiny Smily Story (2022 ver.)]
はい、という訳で、輪堂千速生誕祭、ここまで来てくれたみんな、本当にありがとうございます。
Right, so, for Chihaya Rindo's birthday festival, everyone who came this far, thank you so much.
え、次が、本当にラストの曲です。
Um, the next song is truly the last one.
え、この曲は、いつかみんなと現地で会って、ライブができたときに、最後に歌えたらいいなって、
Um, this song was made with the feeling that I hope we can meet in person someday...
そんな思いで千速のいろんな気持ちを込めて作ってもらった曲です。
and sing it together at the end when we can have a live concert.
千速の初めてのオリジナル曲、聞いてください。「Flat out」
Please listen to Chihaya's very first original song, "Flat out".
メランコリーのリフレイン 午前三時
A melancholy refrain at 3 AM.
夢を見るには少し遅すぎた Midnight
A bit too late to dream, Midnight.
言葉にならないままの想いが
Unexpressed feelings
溢れ出してしまう前に 飛び出した部屋
Before they overflow, I rushed out of the room.
光を見たくて
Wanting to see the light.
“どうせ”“だって”何度だってあきらめようとしたって
No matter how many times I tried to give up saying "oh well" or "but"
だけど“きっど”今日もそっと伸ばした手 あの星まで
Still, today too, I gently reached out my hand toward that star.
自分さえだませない 嘘はもうやめて 踏み込め
I can't even deceive myself, stop the lies, step right in.
駆け抜けて 音も風も置き去って
Run through, leaving sound and wind behind.
迷いさえも振り切って スピードを上げて
Shake off even hesitation, and up the speed.
行かなくちゃ 夜のまだその向こうへ
I have to go, beyond the night.
見たこともない世界へ 今最高速度で
To a world I've never seen, at top speed right now.
高鳴る方へ 答えなんてなくたって ただこうしていたいだけ
Toward the throbbing beat, even if there are no answers, I just want to stay like this.
未完成で完璧な道の先まで 行ける信じて
I believe I can go to the end of this imperfect yet perfect path.
差し障りないように生きた日々
Days lived so as not to cause trouble
諦めの言い訳を探すの止めて
Stop looking for excuses to give up.
もどかしい気持ち窓の向こうに
Frustrating feelings beyond the window
輝くあの星みたいになりたかったんだ
I wanted to be like that shining star.
足りないものだらけだって どれだけ離されたって 止まればそこまでなんだ
Even if I'm full of shortcomings, no matter how far apart, stopping means that's the end.
進め 進め
Advance, advance.
未来を変える瞬間は いつかじゃなくて今なんだ
The moment to change the future is now, not someday.
進め 進め 先へ
Advance, advance, onward.
確かめに行くんだ Flat out
I'm going to find out, Flat out.
駆け抜けて 夢に見たその舞台へ
Run through, to the stage I dreamed of.
決して振り返らないで スピードを上げて
Never look back, up the speed.
行かなくちゃ 夜のまだその向こうへ
I have to go, beyond the night.
見たこともない世界へ 今最高速度で
To a world I've never seen, at top speed right now.
信じる方へ 答えなんてなくたって ただこうして走り出したんだ
Toward what I believe in, even if there are no answers, I just started running like this.
止まらないよ さあ あの星に届け
I won't stop, now, reach that star!
輪堂千速生誕祭2026、見ていただいた皆さん、本当にありがとうございました！
Chihaya Rindo Birthday Festival 2026, thank you all so much for watching!
これからもみんなと向こう側の景色たくさん見に行きたいです！
I want to go see lots of scenery on the other side with everyone from now on too!
これからも千速のことを好きでいてついてきてくれたら嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you continue to like Chihaya and follow along!
本当に今日はありがとうございました！
Thank you all so much for today!
ありがとうねー！
Thank you!
輪堂千隼生誕LIVE お越しいただきありがとうございます
Chihaya Rindou Birthday LIVE - Thank you so much for coming!
初めてのライブはどうでしたか？？
How did you like my very first live show??
見に来てくれたキミといて初めて完成します
It's only complete with you coming to see it.
いつかキミの声が直接きけるその時まで
Until the day I can hear your voice in person,
これからも走り続けるよ！！
I'll keep running forward!!
今日は本当にありがとう
Thank you so much for today!